beautiful.ai 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Beautiful.ai

This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout Beautiful Slides, Inc. (“ **Beautiful.AI** ”) governing Beautiful.AI’s collection and use of personally identifiable information about users of our Beautiful.AI Services that we provide through the use of the Platform and/or Application (collectively, the “ **Services** ”) and users of our websites and blogs (“ **Sites** ”). Capitalized terms not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings given to them in the [**Terms of Service**](https://www.beautiful.ai/terms-of-service).

##### INFORMATION COLLECTION

 _Registration Data_.  In order to use our Services, we require you to submit your personal data to us.  When you register to use our Services, you will be required to provide us with personal data such as your email address and password.  You also have the option to provide us with other personal data, such as your company’s mailing address and your title.

 _Other Data_.  You may also choose to upload personal data and other data into the Services.  If you post any comments on our blogs, we will collect any personal data that you elect to include. You may elect to allow us to access your presentations.

 _Communications Data_.  If you contact us, we will collect any personal data that you include in your communications to us.

 _Aggregate Data_.  The Sites and Services track the total number of visitors to our Site and Services and login times, External Web Sites (as defined below) linked to, browser type, IP addresses.  

 _Sensitive Data.  Beautiful.AI does not collect any “sensitive information” as defined under General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (“_ ** _GDPR_** _”) (e.g. personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, criminal convictions, or personal data concerning health).  
_

##### INFORMATION USE

We use your Registration Data, Other Data and Communications Data to deliver you our Site, the Services and information you have requested, verify your authority to enter certain password protected areas of the Services, detect fraud, illegal activities or security breaches and improve the content and general administration of the Site and our Services.

If you are a user of our Services, we will use your Registration Data, Other Data and Communications Data to provide the Services and support to you.  In order to provide maintenance and updates on our Services, we may need to access your account and may be able to view the presentations and data you have input into the Services.  We also will provide you with notifications about your account and your use of the Services and other services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We use Aggregate Data to better understand how our Site and Services are used and to detect fraud. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the Services, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  We analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate.

See the chart below for our legal basis for processing your personal data.

‍

##### COOKIES AND ONLINE TRACKING

We use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. You can read more about cookies at [**www.allaboutcookies.org**](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

We may set a persistent cookie to store your login data. Persistent cookies enable us to enhance the experience on our Site and Services so you can login without re-entering your account information. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site and Services, but your ability to use some areas of our Site and/or Services may be limited.

Beautiful.AI itself does not track users over time and over multiple websites and does not respond to browser do not track signals. However, third party providers of external services like web traffic analysis services, such as HubSpot and Google Analytics, may track users over time and over our Site, Services and third party apps or websites and such third parties may also place cookies, via our Site and Services.  You can read more about privacy and cookies set by Google Analytics at [**https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/**](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). To learn more about the cookies and other tracking mechanisms that we use, please see our [**Cookie Page**](https://about.beautiful.ai/cookie-policy).  

##### PAYMENT PROCESSING

We do not directly collect your payment information and we do not store your payment information. We use third-party, PCI-compliant, payment processors, which collect payment information on our behalf in order to complete transactions. Our administrators are only able to view limited transaction information via our payment processors’ portals. Please review the privacy policies of our payment processors to learn more about how they collect, process and protect your personal information.  

##### SOCIAL PLUGINS ON OUR SITE

We may use social plugins on our site and may include icons that allow you to interact with third-party social networks such as Google.  For example, you may be able to sign up and login using your Google credentials and we will receive your Google username. The third party social plugin may set a cookie when your browser creates a connection to the servers of such social networks and the plugin may transmit your data to the social networks.

Your use of these social plugins is subject to the privacy policies of the third party social networks.  

##### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Beautiful.AI recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. The Site and Services are not directed to children under the age of 16. Beautiful.AI does not target its Site or Services to children under 16. Beautiful.AI does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 16. If we learn that a child under the age of 16 provided us with personal data, we will delete that information.  If your child has provided personal data, please contact us so we can delete it.  If you are under the age of 16, please do not provide us with any personal data.  

##### DISCLOSURE

We provide your personal data and the data generated by cookies and the aggregate information to certain third parties as follows.

 _Vendors and Service Providers_.  We provide your data to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us in providing our services to you.  For example, we use Google Cloud Hosting to host our Site and Services.  Such third party entities are obligated to use your personal data solely to provide the services to us.  

 _As Required By Law_.  We will disclose your personal data if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to assist in any governmental or law enforcement investigation, to protect our or our users' rights or to enforce our terms of use.

 _Merger or Other Transaction_.  We will not sell your personal data to any company or organization except we may transfer your personal data in conjunction with a transaction such as a financing or to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Beautiful.AI participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Beautiful.AI’s assets to which the Services relate or in the event of a bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings.

 _Other Users_.  You may allow third party collaborators to view your presentations. In such situations, we will provide the third party collaborator with your email address so that they know who requested their collaboration.  

##### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

The Site and Services may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which Beautiful.AI does not have control (" **External Web Sites** ").  Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Beautiful.AI of those External Web Sites.  You acknowledge that Beautiful.AI is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Beautiful.AI is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites.  Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.  

##### SECURITY

We employ industry standard procedural and technological measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your personal data from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.  Beautiful.AI uses secure socket layer, password protection and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personal data.  

##### DATA RETENTION

We will only keep your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

By law we have to keep basic information about our customers, such as payment data, generally for seven years after they stop being customers for tax purposes. Please note that we may retain information that is otherwise deleted in anonymized and aggregated form, in archived or backup copies as required pursuant to records retention obligations, or otherwise as required by law.

In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data; see “Updating and Deleting Your Personal Data” and “Access to Personal Data; Modifications and Corrections; Your Rights” below for further information.  

##### PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

Beautiful.AI may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time.  If so, Beautiful.AI will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site and Services along with a change notice.  Beautiful.AI will also send registered users of our Services a notice that this Privacy Policy has been changed.  Beautiful.AI encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.  Your continued use of the Site and/or Services and/or continued provision of personal data to us after the posting of such notice will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.  

##### NOTICE TO USERS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES

We process and store information on servers located in the United States of America. By using this Site and our Services, you consent to the transfer of your personal data to locations that may be outside of your country of residence, including to the United States of America. In particular, you are advised that the United States of America uses a sectoral model of privacy protection that relies on a mix of legislation, governmental regulation, and self-regulation. The European Union's General Data Protection Regulation (“ **GDPR** ”) allows for transfer of personal data from the European Union to a third country in certain situations. By agreeing to this privacy policy, you agree to the transfer of all such information to the United States of America which may not offer an equivalent level of protection to that required in other countries, particularly the European Union, and to the processing of that information by Beautiful.AI on its servers located in the United States of America as described in this privacy policy. In our discretion, we may adopt other means, such as entering into data processing agreements that include the EU Standard Contractual Clauses, or enter into different certification programs under applicable law for ensuring adequate safeguards.  If you would like to request a data processing agreement from us, please contact us at [**privacy@beautiful.ai.**](mailto:privacy@beautiful.ai)  

##### UPDATING AND DELETING PERSONAL DATA

Beautiful.AI provides you with the ability to review, update and/or delete certain contact information that you provide to us by accessing your account or contacting us.  Your right to access your personal data may be restricted in exceptional circumstances, including, but not limited to, when the burden or expense of providing this access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy in the case in question, or when the rights of persons other than you would be violated by the provision of such access. If we determine that your access should be restricted in a particular instance, we will provide you with an explanation of our determination and respond to any inquiries you may have.  If you are in the European Union, you have additional rights as set forth in the Section below “Access to Personal Data; Modifications and Corrections; Your Rights.”  

##### ACCESS TO PERSONAL DATA; MODIFICATIONS AND CORRECTIONS; YOUR RIGHTS

If you are in the European Union, you have a right to receive confirmation whether personal data concerning the person in question is being processed by us, to receive information about the processing and to access the personal data, and to obtain a copy of the personal data; object to our processing of personal data; have personal data concerning you deleted, and to have incorrect data about you corrected, and to restrict the processing of data concerning you; data portability, meaning that you in certain cases have a right to receive personal data concerning you in a commonly used format, or to have it transmitted to another personal data controller in accordance with your specification; and to not be subject to a decision based only on automatic processing.

Please note that the exercise of these rights is not absolute, and that for some rights certain criteria must be at hand for the right to exercised, or that certain exceptions might be applicable.

Requests sent to privacy@beautiful.ai for personal data access, modification, deletion or correction requests, will be responded to promptly.

You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the supervisory authority for data protection issues in your country of residence. We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the supervisory authority so please contact us in the first instance.  

##### QUESTIONS

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us via email at [**privacy@beautiful.ai**](mailto:privacy@beautiful.ai).

###### ‍

###### ‍
